# SHARJEEL AHSAN

Financial Analyst, MBA (Finance)

Sharjeelahsan007@gmail.com

**91 9528871594** 

Shaheen Bagh, New Delhi, Pin 110025, India.

# **♦ Skills**

Financial Analyst
Spreading
Indexing
Accounting
Team Player
Coordination
Time Management

# Technical Skills

MS Excel MS Word Outlook SAP Adobe DC Citrix

### Interests

Photography Table Tennis Urdu Poetry

#### → Others

Passport availability: Yes Language: English, Hindi, Urdu Notice period: Available to join Immediately

# 

I am an MBA graduate with 3 years of experience in finance. For last 2.5 years, I am working as a Financial Analyst in Commercial Real Estate Mortgage where I am supposed to manage a team in handling all financial documents that are being receiving at preliminary stage of financial analysis.

# Experience

# Silverskills Pvt Ltd, Gurgaon

Financial Analyst

Feb 2019 – July 2021

- o My role involves handling all financial documents such as operating statements, balance sheets, tax returns, audited reports etc that are received in outlook mail box.
- Superficially analysing these documents and then uploading them on client's portal as per their guidelines.
- o Spreading income statement & multifamily rent rolls for various capital sources like FMAC, FNMA, FHA etc.
- o Making Inventory & productivity files on excel.
- o Processing, reviewing, auditing and training staffs.

# 🔵 Genpact India, Gurgaon

Chargeback Analyst

July 2018 - Jan 2019

- o I was working under order to cash cycle for McKesson process.
- My role involved manual reconciliation of chargeback line items using an Excel template.
- o Generating reports from citrix.
- o Working on SAP.

#### Education

Master in Business Administration (Finance) 2016 – 2018 (Aligarh Muslim University, Aligarh)

B. Com (Hons) 2012 – 2015 (Aligarh Muslim University, Aligarh)

### Project

Lean Six Sigma

Project involved time study for IDOC process and reducing the unnecessary steps to optimize the process.

A recommendation was also submitted by me within 7 months of my joining the process and it was in the queue.